Guide to the Jacob Herbert Bruckner papers, 1938-1968.
Bruckner, Jacob Herbert papers, 1938-1968.
- Additional correspondence ( 1963 ), A-Z
  - Dr. Bruckner's Travel Vouchers, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Committee, Board of Traffic Control, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - D, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - E, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - F, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - G, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - H, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - I, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - J, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - James E. Rice Memorial Library, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - K, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - L, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Mc, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - M, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - N, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - O, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - P, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Q, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - R, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - S, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - T, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Miscellaneous subject files
  - Abstarct: Inheritance of Plumage Color in Phasianus Colchius; J.H. Bruckner (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Advisee I.D. Cards (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Advisees, 1969? (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Advisees, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Advisees, Arthur Sidney Dubow, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Advisees, Richard Edward Walesky, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Advisees, Pre Vet, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Advisees, Vet College (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Advisees, Change of Advisor (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Advisees, Change of Registration Forms (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Advisees, Missing Grade Forms (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Advisees, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Africian-American Studies (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Agriculturual Science (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Argrinine (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Biology - Archives (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Biology at Cornell (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Biological Science (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Biological Science (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Breeding for Low Fecundity in the Fowl (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Breeding: Effect of Lights on Low Lines (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Commencement, June 1, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Faculty, Agricultural, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Faculty, University, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Faculty, University, Spring 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Faculty, University, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Faculty, University, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Procedures (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ho Nun De Kah Barbecue (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Li, Lien, Chun (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Library Reserve (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - List of Disciplines (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Malposition - Pheasant (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Mating Lists (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - N.Y.S. College of Agr., Suggestions for Curricula (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - N.Y.S. College of Agr., Dept. of Poultry Science (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Poultry 100, Bruckner (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - N.Y.S. Poultry Production (State Averages) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - N.Y.S. Poultry Improvement Board (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - N.Y.S. Poultry Improvement Board, 1945-1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - N.Y.S. Poultry Improvement Co-Op, 1942-1950 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - N.Y.S. Poultry Improvement Co-Op, 1940-1950 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - N.Y.S. Poultry Improvement Co-Op. By-Laws, etc., 1941-1948 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - N.Y.S. Turkey Growers and Turkey News, 1943-1954 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - News of Graduates of Poultry Dept. (Poultry Club Letters) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Publication Lists - Dept. of Poultry Husbandry (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Registrar - Course, Time and Room Rosters, Spring 1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - James E. Rice Memorial Poultry Library, Cornell University (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - R.O.T.C. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Statler Club (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Turkey - Empire White (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Turkey - Incubation Record (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous items
  - Miscellaneous Items (Box 12)
- File boxes (2), re James E. Rice
  - James E. Rice, Biography (Box 12)
- Loose leaf notebooks
  - Chick Band Book and Lowline Family Record, 1961-1965 (Box 12)
  - Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 12)